A Guide to the Carrie Lee Sizemore papers, 1863-1996, undated
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Carrie Lee Sizemore papers, 1863-1996, undated
The Library of Virginia
52012
.45 cubic feet (1 box)
Sizemore, Carrie Lee
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Lent for copying by Alice F. Daulton, Dinwiddie, Virginia.
Biographical Information
Mary Eliza "Mollie" Fitts was born 3 March 1857 in Halifax County, Virginia, to Samuel J. Fitts (d. 1862) and Almiranda Jane Wilkinson Fitts (Lacy) (1831-1901). She married George Washington Smith (1856-1935) 3 January 1878, and they had 10 children, nine who lived to adulthood. Mollie Fitts Smith died 3 November 1936. Carrie Maude Smith was born 1 September 1880 to Mollie and George W. Smith. Carrie Smith married Charles Edmond Sizemore (1878-1958), and they had six children. Carrie Smith Sizemore died 21 February 1960. Their daughter Carrie Lee Sizemore was born 11 October 1914 and died 24 February 2005.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1863-1996, of Carrie Lee Sizemore of Halifax County, Virginia, consisting of correspondence between members of the Fitts, Smith, Sizemore, Pruitt, Davis, and related families discussing family news and genealogy. Papers also include deeds for property in Mecklenburg County, Virginia, and information on the genealogy of the above-mentioned families and the Tuck family.
Contents List
- Carrie Lee Sizemore papers, 1863-1996, undated., Extent: 12 folders (1 box). (Folder 1-12)
  - Letters, 1874-1877. (Folder 1)
  - Letters, 1901-1911. (Folder 2)
  - Letters, 1925-1929. (Folder 3)
  - Letters, 1931-1936. (Folder 4)
  - Letters, 1966-1967, 1975. (Folder 5)
  - Letters, 1987, 1989. (Folder 6)
  - Letters, 1990, 1996, undated. (Folder 7)
  - Deeds, [1863?], 1869, 1888. (Folder 8)
  - Genealogical papers--Fitts, Jones, Sizemore, Tuck, descent from Pocahontas. (Folder 9)
  - General papers. (Folder 10)
  - Blank postcards and note cards,. (Folder 11)
  - Envelopes (empty). (Folder 12)